class Quiz {
  final String question;
  final String answer;

  Quiz({required this.question, required this.answer});
}

class QuizData {
  static List<Quiz> ebiQuiz = [
    Quiz(question: 'コイ', answer: 'carp'),
    Quiz(question: 'ナマズ', answer: 'catfish'),
    Quiz(question: 'タラ', answer: 'cod'),
    Quiz(question: 'ウナギ', answer: 'eel'),
    Quiz(question: 'ニシン', answer: 'herring'),
    Quiz(question: 'クラゲ', answer: 'jellyfish'),
    Quiz(question: 'サバ', answer: 'mackerel'),
    Quiz(question: 'アシカ', answer: 'seal'),
    Quiz(question: 'アカエイ', answer: 'stingray'),
    Quiz(question: 'イワナ', answer: 'trout'),
    Quiz(question: 'セイウチ', answer: 'walrus'),
    Quiz(question: 'クジラ', answer: 'whale'),
    Quiz(question: 'エイ', answer: 'ray'),
    Quiz(question: '甲殻類', answer: 'crustacean'),
    Quiz(question: 'ザリガニ', answer: 'crayfish'),
    Quiz(question: 'ロブスター', answer: 'lobster'),
    Quiz(question: 'クルマエビ', answer: 'prawn'),
    Quiz(question: 'エラ', answer: 'gills'),
    Quiz(question: 'ウロコ', answer: 'scales'),
    Quiz(question: 'エビのはさみ', answer: 'pincers'),
    Quiz(question: 'アザラシ', answer: 'seal'),
    Quiz(question: 'ホタテ', answer: 'scallop'),
    Quiz(question: 'アワビ', answer: 'abalone'),
    Quiz(question: 'ウミガメ', answer: 'sea turtle'),
    Quiz(question: 'ウニ', answer: 'sea urchin'),
    Quiz(question: 'ナマコ', answer: 'sea cucumber'),
    Quiz(question: 'サンゴ', answer: 'coral'),
    Quiz(question: 'クモヒトデ', answer: 'brittle star'),
    Quiz(question: 'タラバガニ', answer: 'king crab'),
    Quiz(question: 'ハマグリ', answer: 'clam'),
    Quiz(question: 'アオリイカ', answer: 'cuttlefish'),
    Quiz(question: 'シャコ', answer: 'mantis shrimp'),
    Quiz(question: 'ホウボウ', answer: 'gurnard'),
    Quiz(question: 'ギンザメ', answer: 'chimaera'),
    Quiz(question: 'オキアミ', answer: 'krill'),
    Quiz(question: 'ヤドカリ', answer: 'hermit crab'),
    Quiz(question: 'ウミウシ', answer: 'nudibranch'),
    Quiz(question: 'カブトガニ', answer: 'horseshoe crab'),
    Quiz(question: 'ラッコ', answer: 'sea otter'),
    Quiz(question: 'トビウオ', answer: 'flying fish'),
    Quiz(question: 'ダンゴウオ', answer: 'lumpsucker'),
    Quiz(question: 'フサカサゴ', answer: 'lionfish'),
    Quiz(question: 'クモガニ', answer: 'spider crab'),
    Quiz(question: 'ウミサソリ', answer: 'sea scorpion'),
    Quiz(question: 'カイアシ', answer: 'copepod'),
    Quiz(question: 'オワンクラゲ', answer: 'moon jellyfish'),
    Quiz(question: 'ミズクラゲ', answer: 'aurelia jellyfish'),
    Quiz(question: 'ウミクモ', answer: 'sea spider'),
    Quiz(question: 'ウミタナゴ', answer: 'surfperch'),
    Quiz(question: 'タルマワシ', answer: 'pelagic amphipod'),
    Quiz(question: 'ホウネンエビ', answer: 'fairy shrimp'),
    Quiz(question: 'ヨコエビ', answer: 'sand hopper'),
    Quiz(question: 'ムールガイ', answer: 'mussel'),
    Quiz(question: 'イシガキダイ', answer: 'spotted knifejaw'),
    Quiz(question: 'ミノカサゴ', answer: 'scorpionfish'),
    Quiz(question: 'テッポウエビ', answer: 'pistol shrimp'),
    Quiz(question: 'ミズムシ', answer: 'water louse'),
  ];
  static Map<String, String> ebiQuizData = {
    'コイ': 'carp',
    'ナマズ': 'catfish',
    'タラ': 'cod',
    'ウナギ': 'eel',
    'ニシン': 'herring',
    'クラゲ': 'jellyfish',
    'サバ': 'mackerel',
    'アシカ': 'seal',
    'アカエイ': 'stingray',
    'イワナ': 'trout',
    'セイウチ': 'walrus',
    'クジラ': 'whale',
    'エイ': 'ray',
    '甲殻類': 'crustacean',
    'ザリガニ': 'crayfish',
    'ロブスター': 'lobster',
    'クルマエビ': 'prawn',
    'エラ': 'gills',
    'ウロコ': 'scales',
    'エビのはさみ': 'pincers',
    'アザラシ': 'seal',
    'ホタテ': 'scallop',
    'アワビ': 'abalone',
    'ウミガメ': 'sea turtle',
    'ウニ': 'sea urchin',
    'ナマコ': 'sea cucumber',
    'サンゴ': 'coral',
    'クモヒトデ': 'brittle star',
    'タラバガニ': 'king crab',
    'ハマグリ': 'clam',
    'アオリイカ': 'cuttlefish',
    'シャコ': 'mantis shrimp',
    'ホウボウ': 'gurnard',
    'ギンザメ': 'chimaera',
    'オキアミ': 'krill',
    'ヤドカリ': 'hermit crab',
    'ウミウシ': 'nudibranch',
    'カブトガニ': 'horseshoe crab',
    'ラッコ': 'sea otter',
    'トビウオ': 'flying fish',
    'ダンゴウオ': 'lumpsucker',
    'フサカサゴ': 'lionfish',
    'クモガニ': 'spider crab',
    'ウミサソリ': 'sea scorpion',
    'カイアシ': 'copepod',
    'オワンクラゲ': 'moon jellyfish',
    'ミズクラゲ': 'aurelia jellyfish',
    'ウミクモ': 'sea spider',
    'ウミタナゴ': 'surfperch',
    'タルマワシ': 'pelagic amphipod',
    'ホウネンエビ': 'fairy shrimp',
    'ヨコエビ': 'sand hopper',
    'ムールガイ': 'mussel',
    'イシガキダイ': 'spotted knifejaw',
    'ミノカサゴ': 'scorpionfish',
    'テッポウエビ': 'pistol shrimp',
    'ミズムシ': 'water louse',
  };

  static List<Quiz> l1Quiz = [
    Quiz(question: 'リンゴ', answer: 'apple'),
    Quiz(question: 'バナナ', answer: 'banana'),
    Quiz(question: 'サクラ', answer: 'cherry'),
    Quiz(question: 'ブドウ', answer: 'grape'),
    Quiz(question: 'オレンジ', answer: 'orange'),
    Quiz(question: 'モモ', answer: 'peach'),
    Quiz(question: 'ナシ', answer: 'pear'),
    Quiz(question: 'パイナップル', answer: 'pineapple'),
    Quiz(question: 'スイカ', answer: 'watermelon'),
    Quiz(question: 'ニンジン', answer: 'carrot'),
    Quiz(question: 'トマト', answer: 'tomato'),
    Quiz(question: 'ジャガイモ', answer: 'potato'),
    Quiz(question: 'キャベツ', answer: 'cabbage'),
    Quiz(question: 'ブロッコリー', answer: 'broccoli'),
    Quiz(question: 'キュウリ', answer: 'cucumber'),
    Quiz(question: 'トウモロコシ', answer: 'corn'),
    Quiz(question: 'ピーマン', answer: 'green pepper'),
    Quiz(question: 'ナス', answer: 'eggplant'),
    Quiz(question: 'タマネギ', answer: 'onion'),
    Quiz(question: 'ホウレンソウ', answer: 'spinach'),
    Quiz(question: 'コショウ', answer: 'pepper'),
    Quiz(question: 'ショウガ', answer: 'ginger'),
    Quiz(question: 'サトイモ', answer: 'taro'),
    Quiz(question: 'イチゴ', answer: 'strawberry'),
    Quiz(question: 'アボカド', answer: 'avocado'),
    Quiz(question: 'クルミ', answer: 'walnut'),
    Quiz(question: 'アーモンド', answer: 'almond'),
    Quiz(question: 'クッキー', answer: 'cookie'),
    Quiz(question: 'ケーキ', answer: 'cake'),
    Quiz(question: 'アイスクリーム', answer: 'ice cream'),
  ];
  static Map<String, String> l1QuizData = {
    'リンゴ': 'apple',
    'バナナ': 'banana',
    'サクラ': 'cherry',
    'ブドウ': 'grape',
    'オレンジ': 'orange',
    'モモ': 'peach',
    'ナシ': 'pear',
    'パイナップル': 'pineapple',
    'スイカ': 'watermelon',
    'ニンジン': 'carrot',
    'トマト': 'tomato',
    'ジャガイモ': 'potato',
    'キャベツ': 'cabbage',
    'ブロッコリー': 'broccoli',
    'キュウリ': 'cucumber',
    'トウモロコシ': 'corn',
    'ピーマン': 'green pepper',
    'ナス': 'eggplant',
    'タマネギ': 'onion',
    'ホウレンソウ': 'spinach',
    'コショウ': 'pepper',
    'ショウガ': 'ginger',
    'サトイモ': 'taro',
    'イチゴ': 'strawberry',
    'アボカド': 'avocado',
    'クルミ': 'walnut',
    'アーモンド': 'almond',
    'クッキー': 'cookie',
    'ケーキ': 'cake',
    'アイスクリーム': 'ice cream',
    'スープ': 'soup',
    'パン': 'bread',
    'バター': 'butter',
    'チーズ': 'cheese',
    'ヨーグルト': 'yogurt',
    'サラダ': 'salad',
    'スパゲティ': 'spaghetti',
    'ソース': 'sauce',
    'チョコレート': 'chocolate',
    'キャンディ': 'candy',
    'おにぎり': 'rice ball',
    'すし': 'sushi',
    'てんぷら': 'tempura',
    'みそしる': 'miso soup',
    'さしみ': 'sashimi',
    'とうふ': 'tofu',
    'もち': 'rice cake',
    'わさび': 'wasabi',
    'おちゃ': 'green tea',
    'こうちゃ': 'black tea',
    'コーヒー': 'coffee',
    'ジュース': 'juice',
    'みず': 'water',
    'ミルク': 'milk',
    'サケ': 'sake',
  };
}
